Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part II WAG.025.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Immigration, Resettlement and Refugee Aid
  - Subseries IV:A: General Files
    - 1. Topical
      - Chaver Hilf: Letters from Israel, Jun 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 96, Folder 19)
      - Chaver Hilf: Packages to Israel, 1953-1954 (Box 96, Folder 20)
      - Chesad Im Hakdoshim, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 21)
        Microfilm reel#: 288
      - CIO Council, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 22)
      - Citizens Committee on Displaced Persons, 1949-1950 (Box 96, Folder 23)
      - CYCO, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 24)
      - Dachau: Victims, 1950-1954 (Box 96, Folder 25)
      - Deborah Sanatorium, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 26)
      - DiMarco, Mario, 1952-1956 (Box 96, Folder 27)
      - Displaced Persons, 1948-1950 (Box 96, Folder 28)
      - Displaced Persons Act, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 29)
      - Displaced Persons: Arrival Notices, Feb 1949-Apr 1949 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Displaced Persons: Arrival Notices, May 1949-Nov 1949 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Displaced Persons: China (Travel to Israel), undated, 1950 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Diplaced Persons Commission, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Diplaced Persons Commission, Jan 1949-May 1949 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Diplaced Persons Commission, Jun 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Diplaced Persons Commission, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Displaced Persons Commission: Baltic States, 1951 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Displaced Persons Commission: Lists of Arrivals, Mar 1949 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Displaced Persons: Feldafing, undated (Box 97, Folder 10)
        Microfilm reel#: 289
      - Displaced Persons: Germany Card File, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Displaced Persons: ILGWU Project and Questionnaires, 1949 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Displaced Persons: IRRC Reports (A to K), 1948-1949 (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - Displaced Persons: IRRC Reports (L to Z), 1948-1949 (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Displaced Persons: List of Needleworkers, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 15)
      - Employment, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 16)
      - Employment, Jan 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 97, Folder 17)
      - Employment, Sep 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 97, Folder 18)
      - Employment, Jan 1950-Mar 1950 (Box 97, Folder 19)
      - Employment, Apr 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 97, Folder 20)
        Microfilm reel#: 290
      - Employment, Jul 1950-Sep 1950 (Box 97, Folder 21)
      - Employment, Oct 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 97, Folder 22)
      - Employment, Jan 1951-Mar 1951 (Box 97, Folder 23)
      - Employment, Apr 1951-Jul 1951 (Box 97, Folder 24)
      - Employment, Aug 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 97, Folder 25)
      - Employment, Jan 1952-Apr 1952 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Employment, May 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Employment, 1953-1954 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Employment, 1955-1956 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Jan 1948 (Box 98, Folder 5)
        Microfilm reel#: 291
      - Epstein, Lasar, Feb 1948 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Mar 1948 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Apr 1948 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Epstein, Lasar, May 1948 (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Jun 1948 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Jul 1948 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Aug 1948 (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Sep 1948 (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Oct 1948 (Box 98, Folder 14)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Nov 1948 (Box 98, Folder 15)
        Microfilm reel#: 292
      - Epstein, Lasar, Dec 1948 (Box 98, Folder 16)
      - Epstein, Lasar, 1949 (Box 98, Folder 17)
      - Epstein, Lasar, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 18)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Jan 1952-Jun 1952 (Box 98, Folder 19)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Jul 1952-Dec 1953 (Box 98, Folder 20)
      - Epstein, Lasar, 1954-1956 (Box 98, Folder 21)
      - Epstein, Melech, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 22)
      - Federman, Max, 1948 (Box 98, Folder 23)
      - Film: ANos Maisons Enfants@, 1949-1950 (Box 98, Folder 24)
      - Freeland League, 1949-1954 (Box 99, Folder 1)
        Microfilm reel#: 293
      - Friends of the Jewish Labor Committee, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Fund for Refugee Democratic Leaders, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Gal, Luba, 1948-1949 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Germany (letters of thanks and confirmation of received packages), 1948 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Gierowitz, Nathan, 1948 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Godson, Joseph, 1948-1950 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Grade, Chaim and Inna, 1952-1956 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Grand Street Settlement, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Greetings, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - Grossman, Kurt R., 1948 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Gurin, M., 1949-1956 (Box 99, Folder 12)
      - Hebrew Actors Union, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 13)
      - Held, Adolph, 1952-1955 (Box 99, Folder 14)
      - HIAS, 1948-1950 (Box 99, Folder 15)
      - HIAS, 1951-1956 (Box 99, Folder 16)
      - Himmelfarb, Herschel, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 17)
      - Housing: Amalgamated, 1949-1951 (Box 99, Folder 18)
      - Hungary, 1951-1955 (Box 99, Folder 19)
      - Hunger Banquet (Paterson, NJ), 1952 (Box 99, Folder 20)
      - Immigration, 1948-1951 (Box 99, Folder 21)
      - Immigration, Jan 1952-Mar 1952 (Box 99, Folder 22)
      - Immigration, Apr 1952-Jun 1952 (Box 99, Folder 23)
        Microfilm reel#: 294
      - Immigration, Jul 1952-Oct 1952 (Box 99, Folder 24)
      - Immigration, Nov 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 99, Folder 25)
      - Immigration, 1953-1954 (Box 99, Folder 26)
      - Immigration, 1955-1956 (Box 99, Folder 27)
      - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1948-1951 (Box 99, Folder 28)
      - Immigration: Children, 1948 (Box 99, Folder 29)
      - Immigration: Padula, Louis J. (sponsor), 1956 (Box 99, Folder 30)
      - Imtex Parcels, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 31)
      - Integrity of U.S. Citizenship, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 32)
      - International Refugee Organization, 1948-1950 (Box 99, Folder 33)
      - International Rescue and Relief Committee, 1948 (Box 99, Folder 34)
      - International Rescue Committee, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 35)
      - International Rescue Committee, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 1)
        Microfilm reel#: 295
      - International Rescue Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - International Rescue Committee, 1953 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - International Rescue Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - International Rescue Committee: Returnees from Israel, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - International Solidarity Committee, 1948-1950 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Interpreter Releases, 1948 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Interpreter Releases, Jan 1949-May 1949 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Interpreter Releases, Jul 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Interpreter Releases, Jan 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Jewish Daily Forward, 1948-1956 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - Jewish Daily Forward: Sol. Rifkin, 1947-1949 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - Jewish Invalids: Survivors of Nazism, 1954 (Box 100, Folder 13)
        Microfilm reel#: 296
      - Jewish Labor Bund, 1948-1955 (Box 100, Folder 14)
      - Jewish Socialist Verband, 1948-1956 (Box 100, Folder 15)
      - Jewish Teachers' Seminary, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 16)
      - Jewish Telegraphic Agency, 1948-1952 (Box 100, Folder 17)
      - Jewish Vacation Association, 1949 (Box 100, Folder 18)
      - Jewish War Veterans, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 19)
      - Jewish Writers' Union, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 20)
      - Kagan, Solomon, 1949 (Box 100, Folder 21)
      - Kursky Library, Israel, 1954-1955 (Box 100, Folder 22)
      - Landsmanshaftn, 1948 (Box 100, Folder 23)
      - Landsmanshaftn, 1949-1950 (Box 100, Folder 24)
      - Landsmanshaftn, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 25)
      - Landsmanshaftn, 1952-1956 (Box 100, Folder 26)
      - Lang, Lucy Robins, 1948-1954 (Box 100, Folder 27)
      - Lemberger Sick Benevolent Society, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 28)
      - Letters of Appreciation, 1950-1953 (Box 100, Folder 29)
      - Lichtenstein, Zalmon, 1951-1956 (Box 100, Folder 30)
      - Lithuanian Relief Committee, 1952-1956 (Box 100, Folder 30a)
      - Lokiec, Mitchell, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 31)
      - Looping Machines: Knitters, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 32)
      - Manger, Itzik, 1952-1954 (Box 100, Folder 33)
      - Manischewitz Company, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 34)
      - Manoth, Inc., 1952-1953 (Box 100, Folder 35)
      - Matones, Publishing Company, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 36)
      - Matveeff, Ivan, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 37)
      - Meiksin, Bella, 1948 (Box 100, Folder 38)
      - Memos, 1948 (Box 100, Folder 39)
      - Minkoff, N. M., 1949 (Box 101, Folder 1)
        Microfilm reel#: 297
      - Morning Journal, 1950-1951 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Najman, Chil, 1948 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - NCRAC: Committee on Immigration, Jan 1949-Mar 1951 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - NCRAC: Committee on Immigration, Apr 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - NCRAC: Committee on Immigration, Jan 1952-Jun 1952 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - NCRAC: Committee on Immigration, Jul 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - NCRAC: Committee on Immigration, 1954 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - NCRAC: Committee on Immigration, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - NCRAC: Committee on Immigration, 1956 (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - National Council of Jewish Women, 1948-1955 (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - National Surety Corporation, 1950-1952 (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - New Applications: B. Meiksin, 1950 (Box 101, Folder 13)
      - NYANA (New York Association for New Americans, Inc.), 1949-1956 (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - Organek, Rachel, 1950-1951 (Box 101, Folder 15)
      - ORT, 1948-1952 (Box 101, Folder 16)
      - Pat, Jacob, 1948-1953 (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - Patt, Emanuel M.D., 1953 (Box 101, Folder 18)
        Microfilm reel#: 298
      - Peretz Schreiber Farein, 1950-1953 (Box 101, Folder 19)
      - Poale Zion (Germany), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 20)
      - Polish Displaced Persons: Lists, undated (Box 101, Folder 21)
      - Polish Refugees in USSR, undated (Box 101, Folder 22)
      - Polish Rescuers, 1948 (Box 101, Folder 23)
      - Pruziner Relief, 1950-1952 (Box 101, Folder 24)
      - Questionnaires: Refugees in New York (A-E), 1953 (Box 101, Folder 25)
      - Questionnaires: Refugees in New York (F-G), 1953 (Box 101, Folder 26)
      - Questionnaires: Refugees in New York (H-N), 1953 (Box 101, Folder 27)
      - Questionnaires: Refugees in New York (O-Z), 1953 (Box 101, Folder 28)
      - Relative Search, 1948-1951 (Box 101, Folder 29)
      - Relative Search, 1952 (Box 101, Folder 30)
      - Relative Search, 1953, 1956 (Box 101, Folder 31)
      - Relative Search: "Aaufbau", 1948-1954 (Box 102, Folder 1)
        Microfilm reel#: 299
      - Relative Search: Press, 1949 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Relative Search: Press, 1949-1950 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Relative Search: Press, 1951 (Box 102, Folder 3a)
      - Relative Search: Press, 1952 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Relative Search: Press, 1953 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Relative Search: Press, 1954 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Relative Search: Press, 1955 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - Relative Search: Press, 1956 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Relative Search: Radio, 1948 (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - Relative Search: Radio, 1952 (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - Relative Search: Radio, 1953 (Box 102, Folder 11)
      - Relative Search: Radio, 1954 (Box 102, Folder 12)
      - Relative Search: Radio, 1955 (Box 102, Folder 13)
      - Relative Search: Radio, 1956 (Box 102, Folder 14)
      - Report on the Political Situation in the Displaced Persons Camps, 1948 (Box 102, Folder 15)
      - Rescue Fund for Jewish Refugee Writers, 1948 (Box 102, Folder 16)
      - Roumanian Refugees in France, 1950-1952 (Box 102, Folder 17)
      - Salert, Irving, 1949-1952 (Box 102, Folder 18)
      - Silver, George, 1952 (Box 102, Folder 19)
      - Sirotko Fund, 1952 (Box 102, Folder 20)
      - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1955 (Box 102, Folder 21)
      - Stratton Bill: Recent Arrivals - Questionnaires, 1948 (Box 102, Folder 22)
      - Subversive Activities Bill, 1951 (Box 102, Folder 23)
      - Sztern, Efroim, 1948-1949 (Box 102, Folder 24)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, 1949-1955 (Box 102, Folder 25)
      - Tomashower Relief Committee, 1949 (Box 102, Folder 26)
      - Toye, Oscar J. "%Measuring Up" (JLC Boston), 1953 (Box 102, Folder 27)
        Microfilm reel#: 300
      - Tuberculosis Patients, 1952 (Box 102, Folder 28)
      - Union of Russian Jews, 1948-1953 (Box 102, Folder 29)
      - Unions, 1948-1956 (Box 102, Folder 30)
      - Unitarian Service Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 102, Folder 31)
      - United Hebrew Trades, 1955 (Box 102, Folder 32)
      - United Jewish Appeal, 1953-1954 (Box 102, Folder 33)
      - United Service for New Americans, Jan 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 102, Folder 34)
      - United Service for New Americans, Jul 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 102, Folder 35)
      - United Service for New Americans, Jan 1949-May 1949 (Box 102, Folder 36)
      - United Service for New Americans, Jun 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 102, Folder 37)
      - United Service for New Americans, Sep 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - United Service for New Americans, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - United Service for New Americans, 1951-1954 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - U.S. High Commissioner for Germany, 1950-1951 (Box 103, Folder 4)
        Microfilm reel#: 301
      - United Vilner Relief, 1948-1952 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Valdmanis, Alfreds, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Warehouse, 1950-1956 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - AWarsaw Jews Living in the U.S. Zone@, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Workmen's Circle, 1950-1956 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - World Jewish Congress, 1948-1956 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - YIVO (Yiddish Scientific Institute), 1948-1956 (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Zalewitz, Benzion (Bialystoker Landsmanshaft), 1952-1953 (Box 103, Folder 12)
      - Zionism in Displaced Persons Camps, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 13)
      - Zivion, B. (Hoffman), 1951 (Box 103, Folder 14)
      - Zloczower Relief Verband, 1948-1949 (Box 103, Folder 15)
      - Zukunft, 1955-1956 (Box 103, Folder 16)
      - Zurawin, Adam, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - 2. Individual Files, arranged alphabetically by name
      - Abelsky, Tobi Erps, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Abramowicz, Ignacy, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Abrams, William, 1952 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Adler, Lonnie R., 1949 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Ajdelman, Fiszel, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Ajdelman, Izrael, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Ajzenbud, Moishel, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Akerflug, Jankel, undated (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Alperin, Rose, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Anikst, Leib, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - Apfelbaum, Jakob, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Apsan, Anatol, undated (Box 103, Folder 12)
      - Arbeitman, Chaim, 1947-1948 (Box 103, Folder 13)
      - Aszkenazy, Sale, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 14)
      - Ausch, Alexander, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 15)
      - Auszenker, Gershon (Gaushan), 1948 (Box 103, Folder 16)
      - Bainwelzweig, Chaja, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 17)
      - Balabanoff, Angelica, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 18)
      - Bander, Rywka, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 19)
      - Bank, Szaja, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 20)
      - Barabak, Zys, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 21)
      - Baran, Abram, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 22)
      - Barban, David, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 23)
      - Beilis, Fiszel, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 24)
      - Bekerman, Mojsze, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 25)
      - Beniamin, Nachman (Nechama), 1948 (Box 103, Folder 26)
      - Berliner, Ester, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 27)
      - Berlinski, Chiel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 28)
      - Bermansohn, Lejb, 1948-1949 (Box 103, Folder 29)
      - Bernath, Emanuel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 30)
      - Bernstein, Aron, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 31)
      - Bernstein, David Solomon, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 32)
      - Bialoglowski, Abram, 1948-1951 (Box 103, Folder 33)
      - Bilinski, Romauld and Krystyna, 1954-1955 (Box 103, Folder 34)
      - Binker, Izak, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 35)
      - Birenbaum, Bela, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 36)
      - Birenhak, Jacob, 1948-1949 (Box 103, Folder 37)
      - Birnbaum, Lazar, undated (Box 103, Folder 38)
      - Bliskowski, Leon, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 39)
      - Bloch, Mojaze, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 40)
      - Blum, Boris, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 41)
      - Boczkiewicz, Reubin, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 42)
      - Bojman, Israel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 43)
      - Boms, Abram, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 44)
      - Bonk, Jacob, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 45)
      - Borichowsky, Jakob, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 46)
      - Bracker, Moniek, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 47)
      - Brandl, Benjamin, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 48)
      - Brandwajn, Moses, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 49)
      - Brecher, Chaim, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 50)
      - Brener, Mojsze, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 51)
      - Bressler, David, 1947, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 52)
      - Brettschneider, Isser, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 53)
      - Brodt, Abraham-Izak, undated (Box 103, Folder 54)
      - Bruell, Fanny, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 55)
      - Brysk, Henri, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 56)
      - Bugalski, Selig, undated (Box 103, Folder 57)
      - Burdowski, David, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 58)
      - Butkowski, Abram, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 59)
      - Buzinover, Aron, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 60)
      - Caban, Nathan, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 61)
      - Caprino, Umberto (Italian Visa), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 62)
      - Celemensji, Anna, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 63)
      - Celemenski, Jacob, 1948-1953 (Box 103, Folder 64)
      - Celemenski, Moishe, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 65)
      - Celnik, Jacob, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 66)
      - Cenower, Cecelia, undated (Box 103, Folder 67)
      - Chadajo, Leon and Symatow, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 68)
      - Chajaytnski, Faja Swiderska, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 69)
      - Chajet, Feivel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 70)
      - Charlash, Icchok, 1951-1953 (Box 103, Folder 71)
      - Chewlin, Leiba, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 72)
      - Chmelewski, Ester, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 73)
      - Chodos, Herschel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 74)
      - Chojnacki, Wolf, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 75)
      - Chojnowski, Icchok, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 76)
      - Chrzonstowski, Max, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 77)
      - Chwytejko, Abram, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 78)
      - Ciemny, Mejlach, 1949-1950 (Box 103, Folder 79)
      - Crun, Etu, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 80)
      - Crzonstowski, Mojsze, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 81)
      - Cukier, Joel and Frajda, 1952 (Box 103, Folder 82)
      - Cygielman, Lejb-Lea, 1951-1953 (Box 103, Folder 83)
      - Cygielman, Leon, 1956 (Box 103, Folder 84)
      - Cymbac, Hela, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 85)
      - Dallin, David J., 1949-1950 (Box 103, Folder 86)
      - Dankgot, Alter, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 87)
      - Dauman, Samuel, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 88)
      - Davidowitz, Alexander, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 89)
      - Davidson, Abram, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 90)
      - Degenszajn, Szlama, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 91)
      - Dindas, Tobias, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 92)
      - Dobrzynski, Abram, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 93)
      - Dorfberger, Benjamin and Rubin, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 94)
      - Dreilich, Mania, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 95)
      - Dzienciolowski, Symcha, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 96)
      - Edberg, Jakob, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 97)
        Microfilm reel#: 302
      - Eder, Israel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 98)
      - Ehrenfried, Doris T., 1955 (Box 103, Folder 99)
      - Eichenbaum, Isucher, 1951, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 100)
      - Eidlisz, Herman, 1952-1953 (Box 103, Folder 101)
      - Eisenberg, Rosa, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 102)
      - Eisenman, Jakob, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 103)
      - Eizman, Leon, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 104)
      - Elenbojgen, Perla, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 105)
      - Elenzweig, Israel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 106)
      - Ellin, Nathan, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 107)
      - Elson, Debora, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 108)
      - Epstein, Lotte, 1953-1954 (Box 103, Folder 109)
      - Erenstein, Jacob, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 110)
      - Erlichman, Herez, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 111)
      - Erlichman, Moses, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 112)
      - Erps, Sophie, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 113)
      - Eskenazi, Simon, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 114)
      - Faitek, Bernard, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 115)
      - Fajersztain, Arnold, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 116)
      - Fajwlowicz, Nordko, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 117)
      - Falikovic, Samuel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 118)
      - Farkas, Sandor, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 119)
      - Fasenfest, Markus, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 120)
      - Fechtner, Joseph, undated (Box 103, Folder 121)
      - Federbush, Anna, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 122)
      - Federman, Bronia, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 123)
      - Feifowicz, Rafeal, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 124)
      - Feiges, Solomon, undated (Box 103, Folder 125)
      - Feinblut, Moses, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 126)
      - Feiner, Aron, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 127)
      - Feldman, Cyla, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 128)
      - Feldman, Israel, 1947 (Box 103, Folder 129)
      - Ferdman, Nusin, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 130)
      - Fershko, Chaim and Sara, undated (Box 103, Folder 131)
      - Feuerwerk, Berek, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 132)
      - Fingerhut, Lejba and Mendel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 133)
      - Fiszman, Yankiel Hersz, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 134)
      - Fixler, Eva and Leopold, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 135)
      - Flam, Joseph Alexandre, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 136)
      - Flaum, Mina, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 137)
      - Fleiszer, Simon, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 138)
      - Fogel, David and Chil, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 139)
      - Fraiman, Frieda, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 140)
      - Freiman, Wanda, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 141)
      - Frenkel, Szmuel-Lejb, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 142)
      - Frenkiel, Dawid, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 143)
      - Fridman, Chaya, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 144)
      - Friedman Lebouitz, Sonja, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 145)
      - Frischman, Kalman, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 146)
      - Frydman, Derek and Gabriel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 147)
      - Fryszdorf, Chana, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 148)
      - Fuchs, Sigmunt, undated (Box 103, Folder 149)
      - Fuks, Chaim Leib, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 150)
      - Furzspan, Aron, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 151)
      - Gajer, David, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 152)
      - Gamer, Helen, 1952 (Box 103, Folder 153)
      - Ganz, Elias, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 154)
      - Gelczynski, Isak, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 155)
      - Gelczynski, Rosa, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 156)
      - Gelczynski, Szepel, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 157)
      - Gelzynska, Samuel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 158)
      - Gensel, Aron, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 159)
      - Gerstmann, Meyer, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 160)
      - Gersztman, Motek, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 161)
      - Glaser, Bernard, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 162)
      - Gleitman, Josef, undated (Box 103, Folder 163)
      - Glicker, Salomon, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 164)
      - Glikowski, Mozes, undated (Box 103, Folder 165)
      - Gliksman, Jakob, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 166)
      - Glikstein, Abraham, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 167)
      - Glikstein, Izaak, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 168)
      - Goldbaum, Leibl and Chaim, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 169)
      - Goldberg, Dawid, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 170)
      - Goldberg, Josif, undated (Box 103, Folder 171)
      - Goldberg, Mojaze, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 172)
      - Goldberg, Mordke, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 173)
      - Goldberg, Wolf, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 174)
      - Goldbat (Fibich) Felix and Judith, 1951-1956 (Box 103, Folder 175)
      - Goldchecht, Cyrla, undated (Box 103, Folder 176)
      - Goldhersz, Motel, undated (Box 103, Folder 177)
      - Goldman, Abraham, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 178)
      - Goldman, Aron, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 179)